<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://plutotin.github.io/osmosfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-08-27T16:22:50.643Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://plutotin.github.io/osmosfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://plutotin.github.io/osmosfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google seems to disable some AI features on Pixel 9 when the bootloader is unlocked]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637900</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/google-pixel-9-ai-features-bootloader-unlocked/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main focus of Google’s new Pixel 9 series is on AI, with several new features taking advantage of the rapidly growing tech. However, if you unlock your bootloader, many of the Pixel 9’s new AI apps will stop working.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Music AI conversational radio sees wider testing]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637927</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/youtube-music-ai-conversational-radio/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in July, YouTube Music announced that it was testing an AI-generated conversational radio and the prompt-based feature is seeing wider availability. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on with every official Pixel 9 series case: Worth the money? [Video]]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=636407</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/pixel-9-official-cases/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With brand-new phones come brand-new accessories. Is getting an official Pixel 9 case going to mean pixel-perfect, and do these first-party accessories make financial sense?
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damien Wilde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deals: Pixel 8a $450, Galaxy A35 $300, 1TB Samsung microSD new low, 4-pack Samsung SmartTag 2 $60, more]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637903</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/deals-pixel-8a-galaxy-1tb-microsd-smarttag-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s deals are now at the ready starting with a return of Prime Day pricing on the 2024 Google Pixel 8a handset at $449 shipped in all four colorways, and on both the 128GB and 256GB models. That deal also sits alongside a return low on the Samsung 2024 unlocked Galaxy A35 smartphone at $100 off, as well as Samsung’s brand new 180MB/s 1TB Pro Plus microSD card to expand your storage at its best price yet. You can also land a sweet deal on a 4-pack of Samsung SmartTag 2 item trackers at $60 – that’s $15 a pop – as well as a host of discounts on charging gear, the new Elgato Neo USB-C microphone, smart bulbs, and much more. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Kahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now buy almost every NFL team’s official Galaxy Z Flip 6 case]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637867</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/nfl-teams-official-galaxy-z-flip-6-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is still offering official cases for the Galaxy Z Flip 6. The newest additions include Flipsuit cases for the Galaxy Z Flip 6 showcasing the logo of almost every NFL team.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Romero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tecno’s Phantom V Fold 2 and Flip 2 leak with better designs, prices under ~$1,000]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637862</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/tecno-phantom-v-fold-flip-2-leak/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tecno is one of the unexpected names in the foldable space, with its Phantom V Fold and Flip lines costing way less than the competition. Soon, the company is set to launch the Tecno Phantom V Fold 2 and Flip 2, and they look way better despite not costing as much as the competition.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in the August 2024 Google System Updates [U: 8/26]]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=633909</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/august-2024-google-system-updates/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The monthly “Google System Release Notes” primarily detail what’s new in Play services, Play Store, and Play system update across Android phones/tablets, Wear OS, Google/Android TV, Auto, and PC. Some features apply to end users, while others are aimed at developers.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus 13 rumored to bring a 6,000mAh battery]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637819</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/oneplus-13-rumored-6000mah-battery/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus has always been one of the most forward-thinking companies in terms of charging speeds and power, and with the OnePlus 13 on the horizon, there’s no reason the company should give that up. New leaks suggest the OnePlus 13 will bring a 6,000mAh battery and fast charging.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Romero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing appears to be working on a new pair of ‘Ear Open’ earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637812</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/nothing-ear-open-earbuds-leak/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing makes some of the best earbuds out there, and the company appears to be working to add to its lineup with the “Ear Open” surfacing this week.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel may soon get a revamped ‘Wallpaper & style’ page [Video]]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637813</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/27/google-pixel-wallpaper-android-15-redesign/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google appears to be working on a new “Wallpaper & style” page for Pixel phones and tablets which reorganizes existing options for a streamlined UI.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 15 Pixel update officially launching in October [U]]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637697</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/android-15-pixel-update-date/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T04:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Beta 4.2 two weeks ago, Google has finished testing Android 15 and is already moving on to QPR1. However, a new report today says Android 15 will not roll out to Pixel devices until October.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Tasks redesign rolls out with cards, drops bottom app bar]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637754</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/google-tasks-redesign-android/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Tasks was updated with Material You in February of 2023, and a substantial redesign today overhauls the Android app further.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shared drives rolling out to Google Workspace Business Starter next month]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637750</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/google-workspace-business-starter-shared-drives/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T23:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May of 2023, Google announced that the Workspace Business Starter tier was switching to pooled storage, with shared drives set to launch next month.  
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome now vibrates when you pull-to-refresh on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637742</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/chrome-android-refresh-vibrates/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you pull-to-refresh a page in Chrome 128, your Android phone will now subtly vibrate to acknowledge the action.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Meet will open Picture-in-Picture when you switch tabs]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637736</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/google-meet-auto-pip/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Google Meet introduced an upgraded Picture-in-Picture experience for desktop Chrome that will now automatically open when you switch tabs.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixel 9 Pro Fold that arrived early gets unboxing, ships unfolded [Gallery]]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637723</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/pixel-9-pro-fold-unboxing/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pixel 9 Pro Fold officially hits store shelves on September 4, but one lucky person received theirs early and unboxed it.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts Galaxy Watch trade-in values alongside discounts for students]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637678</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/samsung-galaxy-watch-trade-in-student-discounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Summer break comes to an end for many students across the US, Samsung has announced new discounts available for students as well as improved trade-in offers towards Galaxy Watch.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android game and app price drops: Fran Bow, Leo’s Fortune, Super Onion Boy 2, more]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/android-game-app-price-drops-fran-bow/</id>
        <link href="https://9to5toys.com/2024/08/26/android-game-app-price-drops-fran-bow/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This afternoon’s collection of the best Android game and app deals is now up for grabs with notable price drops now at the ready courtesy of Google Play. Here’s how to score $100 off your Galaxy Buds 3/Pro 3 with purchases of the Galaxy Z Flip 6 alongside notable deals on Bose’s latest world-class QuietComfort buds and headphones, as well as one of the best prices yet on the Motorola MA1 Wireless Android Auto Adapter. As for the apps, highlights include titles like Fran Bow, Leo’s Fortune, Super Onion Boy 2, Ailment, and more. Head below for today’s best price drops and freebies. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>9to5Toys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chat adds support for IFTTT integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637688</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/google-chat-ifttt/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chat now integrates with IFTTT (if this, then that) to power various automations. This is available for both Google Workspace and personal accounts. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abner Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 9 launches ‘Adaptive Touch,’ improves screen sensitivity while wet, etc]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637614</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/google-pixel-9-adaptive-touch-feature/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through a new software option on the Pixel 9 series, you might find it easier to use Google’s smartphones while the touchscreen is wet, has a screen protector on, or has other hurdles in place that might impact the functionality.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deals: Bose QuietComfort headphones and buds up to $100 off, Android Auto Adapter $36, magnetic charging gear, more]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637672</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/deals-bose-ultra-headphones-android-auto-adapte/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your Monday deals are now ready to go down below starting off with some notable price drops on the latest Bose QuietComfort Ultra Wireless Earbuds and headphones with as much as $100 in savings – be sure to check out the new diamond colorways that were unveiled today as well. From there, we spotted one of the lowest prices yet on the Motorola MA1 Wireless Android Auto Car Adapter at $36 alongside a $100 price drop on OnePlus 12 with a FREE pair of $180 Buds Pro 2, notable offers on Galaxy Z Flip 6 and Galaxy Buds 3/Pro 3, plenty of charger and cable deals, and more. Head below for a closer look. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Kahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honor is building its own AI suite on the Magic V3 with the help of Google Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637654</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/honor-ai-suite-magic-v3-google-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honor announced the Magic V3 some time ago in China, breaking thickness records in the foldable space. Now, the company is announcing several new apps in partnership with Google Cloud that will bring some extra productivity powered by AI.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Romero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Watch 4 gets fourth One UI 6 beta update, AOD now works everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637639</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/galaxy-watch-4-one-ui-6-beta-update-aod/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s One UI 6 is the company’s newest OS based on Wear OS 5, and it has been rolling out to older watch generations in a beta phase. The Galaxy Watch 4 is getting an update to the One UI 6 beta that allows always-on display (AOD) to run anywhere on the watch.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Romero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Pixel 9 Pro XL buyers run into wireless charging issues, including on Pixel Stand]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637620</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/google-pixel-9-pro-xl-wireless-charging-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just purchased a new Pixel 9 Pro XL from Google and have run into strange issues while wireless charging, you’re not alone.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schoon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Tab S10 Ultra and Plus leak shows more of the same]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/?p=637616</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2024/08/26/galaxy-tab-s10-leaks-show-tablets-side-by-side/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new set of images showcasing the Galaxy Tab S10 series has popped up in new leaks. The new series seems to drop the basic model and opts for two familiar sizes.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Romero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>